

I'm a designer with 8+ years of professional experience in design. My experience spans from graphic and visual design to designing user experiences and solving complex interaction, architecture, and usability issues. I'm also an expert at HTML/CSS and have built and released a variety of projects spanning in size from private business websites to mid-size e-commerce and technology platforms. I have a passion for learning and read a lot of behavioral psychology books in exploration of how humans think, which I try to apply to my work when designing products for human interaction.

Skills & Expertise

Design Tools	User Experience	Development	Research
 Adobe XD/CS 	Wireframing	HTML5 / CSS3	UserTesting
Sketch	Prototyping	JavaScript	 Optimal
Axure	User Flows	jQuery	Workshop
 Balsamiq 	 Architecture 	Bootstrap	 Google Analytics
InVision	Personas	Git / GitHub	 UsabilityHub
• Figma	User Testing	Jira / BitBucket	 Google Forms
Draw.io	 Agile/Scrum 		

Recent Projects

Family Law of Seattle | Seattle, WA

Product Designer / Developer | 2/2018 - 5/2018

Redesigned the law firms' website end to end. Work included research and strategic analysis, user experience and process work, sketches and wireframes, design and comps, and development of responsive website with booking form and google map integration.

Prep Sportswear | Seattle, WA

UI Developer & Architecture Consultant | 5/2016 - 4/2017

Developed the responsive front-end of the company's new e-commerce and fundraising platform and their corresponding websites. Consulted with engineers during building of information architecture. Designed style guide using an atomic approach for visual design of new sites in alignment with design team. Designed and fixed web apps to aid processes of internal users.

Work Experience

Self Employed / Freelance | Seattle, WA

Product Designer | 5/2017 - Current

Designed, developed, and updated websites for local small businesses. Worked on small design and branding projects.

Prep Sportswear | Seattle, WA

Graphic / UX Designer | 1/2013 - 5/2016

Designed and/or redesigned tools and company workflows with engineering team to successfully improve efficiency and capabilities of internal users throughout the company, resulting in over 25% reduction of production error and vastly improved process efficiency. Worked with marketing team to design strategies and visual pages and assets for campaigns and partnerships. Designed and built new set of marketing and transactional email templates. Created web assets and graphic content for website.

Jr. Graphic Designer | 6/2010 - 1/2013

Designed collections of templates for apparel application. Oversaw bulk design creation by an overseas design team in Russia. Created illustrations and icons for design collections. Managed and improved folder structures of design collections. Managed all design errors and worked with engineers to fix and maintain processing tools.

Education

Bachelor's of Arts – Graphic Design w/ Honors | University of Redlands

Bachelor's of Arts – Business Admin & Management | University of Redlands

Technical Training

Bloc | Remote

UX Design Apprenticeship | 8/2017 - 5/2018

Project based remote UX program that applies an end-to-end UX cycle to self-guided projects throughout the track (research through development). Projects included building a crowdfunding platform, and a cloud storage website.

Team Treehouse | Remote

Front-End Development Track | 1/2016 - 4/2016

Learned advanced HTML/CSS, beginning JavaScript, Microsoft Visual Studio/MVC.

School of Visual Concepts | Seattle, WA

HTML/CSS for Email | 8/2017 - 5/2018

Learned basic HTML/CSS for responsive email development, testing software, mail clients.

Web Design & Wireframing | 2009

Learned wireframing and basic site architecture through project work.